Good morning, the current time is 3:06 AM.
Today I'd like to share with you a day in my life on The Time.
Here are my pajamas today.
Nami Inoue gave me these as a Christmas present.
They are so fluffy!
I've finished getting dressed and it's time for me to leave the house.
I'd like to go to TBS now.
I'm going to TBS now.
I always check the script while I'm having my make-up done.
After work in the morning.
They've done my makeup and everything.
So all I have to do is go out.
That's why I always go out on Nakayama day.
Lately, I'm really into going to the movies.
Last week, I went to see three movies.
Spy Family and Golden Camry.
In this closed snowy
In the Snowy Villa
All of them were fun.
Oh, no, I saw four.
And Sacchan...
We also came to see Conan's movie together.
You saw four last week.
That's great.
That's the best ever.
Oh, while I was writing and talking...
It all happened so fast.
My hair is very active.
I don't know what to call it.
I don't know what to say.
It's so lively... your hair.
Yes, sir.
This is the breakfast that you always prepare for us.
They prepare many kinds of breakfast every morning.
I choose one from here and eat it.
But I get sleepy after eating.
I eat it after the program is over.
Which one should I choose today?
And here is the snack corner. I don't eat before the show.
I don't eat before the show, but I always have some snacks here to fill my stomach.
This is my toothpaste set that I forgot last week.
I'll take care of it.
How about today's outfit?
This one-piece dress or this one-piece dress.
Or this one.
I think this one is better.
The clothes are really cute. I can't choose.
I always let the staff decide for me.
Today...
I'll choose this one.
The first one.
It's changed.
Today.
It's like this.
It's a down coat, but it's still soft and fluffy.
I'm going to be on the weather in the morning.
I'll be dressed like this.
I've decided if I'm going to put it in or not.
I may have forgotten about this, but if you can make it real, you can sing it.
I understand. That's what Azumi told me to do.
I guess you did what came to you in a flash.
Did you come up with the idea after you started appearing on "The Time"? Did he do it for you? No, I...
Since I've been on "THE TIME".
I've been able to crack open some common sense issues.
I don't always know about things that I should know about.
When I went back to my parents' house at the beginning of the year...
My mother had about three books
My mother bought me about 3 books like "Common Sense Book for Adults" and told me to read them because she found out on TV that I have no common sense.
She told me that I should read this book anyway, because she knew from TV that I had no common sense.
It's about 6 o'clock now.
I'm leaving the school at 6:00 a.m.
I'll tell you about the weather in the morning.
I'll tell you the weather in the morning, so I'm heading outside now.
It's very cold in the morning.
So...
I wonder if I can sleep.
Actually, I've got circuits in my stomach and back.
I always have circuits installed in my stomach and back.
Have a good day.
I'll see you later.
Good morning, sir.
It's 6:30 in the morning.
This hour is with Michi Ichinose of Nogizaka46.
Compared to yesterday, it's a lot colder.
Yes, I was here yesterday as well.
The coldness is totally different.
It's going to be cold during the day today.
It's good to have down coat, scarf, and gloves.
Don't let today's coldness get the better of you.
I'm going to the studio now.
I'm going to the studio now!
me
me, me, me...
I was nervous today.
I heard something I've never heard before.
I learned a lot.
I got to know the other announcers pretty well.
They kept asking me why my head was so screwed up.
That's right.
The announcers are always really nice to me.
They would talk to me during breaks and free time.
And they teach me a lot of things.
I really cherish that time.
I'm always so grateful for their kindness.
This is how I do it.
I'd like to share with you my morning routine.
I'd like to introduce you to my morning routine.
How did you like it?
Get up early.
I'd like to make Wednesday mornings
I'd like to make Wednesday mornings more exciting.
I hope you all wake up early too!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating. See you soon.